Blood Money. Deadly Heist. Some things can make a guy crazy.
Stark Raving Mad is a comedy, crime, action film directed by Drew Daywalt.
A crook quietly plots his revenge against the boss who
murdered his brother while working for him.
Ben McGewan, played by Seann William Scott.
Rikki Simms, played by Timm Sharp.
Jeffery Jay, played by Patrick Been.
Jake Nealson, played by John B. Crye.
Betty Shin, played by Suzy Nakamura.
Gregory, played by Lou Diamond Phillips.
Stark Raving Mad is a 2002 American heist comedy film directed and written by Drew Daywalt
and David Schneider and starring Seann William Scott and Lou Diamond Phillips.
The film follows thief Ben McGewan (Scott), who organizes a rave
at a nightclub in order to mask a bank heist.
The film's soundtrack was composed by John Digweed.
The film explores themes of transvestite, bank, nightclub.
The tone is lighthearted.